heartbeat.my 2018-06-29

# Privacy Statement

**Introduction  
**We know your privacy is important to you and HeartBeat.my is committed to protecting your information. 

**The information we need  
**When you place an order, we will ask for your contact information (i.e., name, shipping address, and email address). The information you provide us is used for processing and fulfilling your order and contacting you if we have problems processing your order. 

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law and when we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process. 

**What we do with your information**  
The private information that you give us when you place an order or utilize one of our special services is used to process and fulfill your order or request. This information may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more helpful and relevant to you. 

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law and when we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process. 

**Our Commitment**  
HeartBeat.my is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the personal information you give us, such as your billing, shipping and email addresses, to process and keep you informed of your order. You may, from time to time, receive information from us about new features, new services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. Under no circumstances do we rent, trade or share your email address with any other company for marketing purposes. However, we do make our mailing list available to carefully screened companies whose products or services might interest you. 

**Choice to opt-out**  
If you are no longer interested in receiving announcements and other marketing information from us, please email your request to Admin@HeartBeat.my. Please include your complete name and mailing address (as well as your email address) if you prefer not to receive newsletters from us. 

**Updating your personal information**  
If your personal information changes, we provide you a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you provided to us. You can make necessary changes by contacting our customer service department via email at: admin@HeartBeat.my. **  
**
